<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 12:40:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ZiggorX.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Government Surveillance necessary for national security?</title><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/articles/govsurveillance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 12:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ZiggorX.github.io/articles/govsurveillance/</guid><description>Government surveillance is necessary and spying on internet traffic and search history of citizens is in the interest of national security.  Contents Opening statement Arguement Closing statement References Opening statement National security is an important concept that applies to every individual in our current societal infrastructures. Our confidence in our government can become compromised if our security is breached and we do not discover threats before they are enacted.</description></item><item><title>About this page</title><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/about/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 16:51:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ZiggorX.github.io/about/about/</guid><description>FILL IN DETAILS</description></item><item><title>USB Recon Tool: 1st year project</title><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/uniprojects/usbrecontool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 16:39:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ZiggorX.github.io/uniprojects/usbrecontool/</guid><description>-AEC- ALL Notes:
Contents Recon Useful information Purpose of information Communication of Data HTTP FTP Server FTP Server Types Configuration Update Linux Install and Start VSFTPD Configuring VSFTPD Anon FTP Inotify and Linux services Commands (Status) Server-side permissions chroot Client (winSCP) Dealing with the Data Windows Structure File System Log Files Comparison to Linux Autorun Feature (EXT) Privelege escalation XP Service packs Why did we choose this?</description></item><item><title>SkillsTest V1</title><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/tutorials/skillstest-v1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:18:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ZiggorX.github.io/tutorials/skillstest-v1/</guid><description>245 Skills test - Notes System 1 Target IP Address: 192.168.118.130 Open ports: 21 FTP (Anon allowed) 22 SSH 25 SMPT 80 HTTP (Werkzeug httpd 1.0.1)+(Python 3.9.0) 4444 krb254? (FourOhFourRequest) - Still gives 200 ok? 8080 HTTP (Apache/2.4.38 Debian) 1 service unrecognised (Linux kernel | HTTP requests) ┌──(user㉿kali)-[~] └─$ nmap -A 192.168.118.130 Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-03-27 12:19 GMT Nmap scan report for 192.</description></item><item><title>Social Engineering and Reconnaisance</title><link>https://ZiggorX.github.io/articles/reconse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:01:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ZiggorX.github.io/articles/reconse/</guid><description>Contents Introduction Social Engineering Technical implementation SE Real world example SE Wider security context SE Mitigation of the problem Social, Legal and Ethical considerations SE Reconnaissance Technical implementation recon Real world example recon Wider security context recon Mitigation of the problem recon Social, Legal and Ethical considerations recon Summary References Introduction This report will cover two common topics related to cyber security, reconnaissance and social engineering, both of which are in similar phases of the Ethical Hacking process, meaning that we can analyse the links and implementations of them in regards to each other.</description></item></channel></rss>