<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on</title><link>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 14:55:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://C-Security.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leading and Developing people: Advantage Module</title><link>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/leadinganddeveloping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 14:55:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/leadinganddeveloping/</guid><description>Leading and Developing people. Contents Team Leadership theories Monitoring and managing performance of teams and individuals Methods for identifying skills and knowledge requirements of people, and how to meet the identified needs. How can a leader create a high performing team? References Team Leadership theories Team leadership theories have become the key element in understanding how an individual is able to effectively manage and administrate a group of individuals to become a team that can work concurrently and efficiently, with an emphasis on developing and nurturing growth within the environment they find themselves working in, irrespective of personal backgrounds, ability and overall work ethicises.</description></item><item><title>Is Government Surveillance necessary for national security?</title><link>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/govsurveillance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 12:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/govsurveillance/</guid><description>Contents Opening statement Arguement Closing statement References Opening statement National security is an important concept that applies to every individual in our current societal infrastructures. Our confidence in our government can become compromised if our security is breached and we do not discover threats before they are enacted. The national security and intelligence organisation claim that they are responsible for ‘providing advice to the national security council, coordinating and developing foreign and defence policy across government and coordinating ethical and legal issues across the intelligence community’ (Gov, n.</description></item><item><title>Social Engineering and Reconnaisance</title><link>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/reconse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:01:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://C-Security.github.io/articles/reconse/</guid><description>Contents Introduction Social Engineering Technical implementation SE Real world example SE Wider security context SE Mitigation of the problem Social, Legal and Ethical considerations SE Reconnaissance Technical implementation recon Real world example recon Wider security context recon Mitigation of the problem recon Social, Legal and Ethical considerations recon Summary References Introduction This report will cover two common topics related to cyber security, reconnaissance and social engineering, both of which are in similar phases of the Ethical Hacking process, meaning that we can analyse the links and implementations of them in regards to each other.</description></item></channel></rss>